Guide to the Robert Watts Hudgens Papers, 1925-1973 RL.00584
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Robert Watts Hudgens Papers, 1925-1973, 25 boxes
  - Rural Development Associates: 1964 (Box 18)
  - Rural Housing Alliance: 1970-1973 (Box 18)
  - Rushton, Marion: 1949-1959 (Box 18)
  - Russell, John MacFarlane: 1954-1964 (Box 18)
  - Russell, Richard Brevard: 1955 (Box 18)
  - Ryerson, Knowles Augustus: 1958 (Box 18)
  - Santiago College: 1958-1960 (Box 18)
  - Sarah Lawrence College: 1952 (Box 18)
  - Scarlett, William: 1944-1957 (Box 18)
  - Senior, Clarence: 1961 (Box 18)
  - Shepherd, George William: Sept. [?] (Box 18)
  - Shuff, Charles Henry: 1964 (Box 18)
  - Shultz, Sonia: 1963-1964 (Box 18)
  - Slade, Charles: 1947-1949 (Box 18)
  - Smith, Raymond Charles: 1952-1971 (Box 18)
  - Smith, Russell: 1951 (Box 18)
  - Snyder Family (Raub and Florence Snyder): 1963-1972 (Box 18)
  - Society for International Development: 1959-1962 (Box 19)
  - Society for International Development: 1963-1965 (Box 19)
  - Society for International Development: 1966-1972 (Box 19)
  - Southeast Public Health Foundation: 1965-May, 1966 (Box 19)
  - Southeast Public Health Foundation: 1966, June-Dec. (Box 19)
  - Southeast Public Health Foundation: 1967-1969 (Box 19)
  - Southeast Public Health Foundation: 1970-1972 (Box 19)
  - Spetland, Olaf H.: 1963 (Box 19)
  - Stevenson, Adlai Ewing: 1958 (Box 19)
  - Stimson Family (Philip Moen and Elizabeth B. Stimson): 1956-1970 (Box 19)
  - Strand Family (Walter and Betty Strand): 1963-1970 (Box 19)
  - Stryker, Roy E.: 1960-1970 (Box 19)
  - Stubbs Family (Thomas M, and Bee Stubbs): 1970-1972 (Box 19)
  - Survey of International Development: 1966-1972 (Box 20)
  - Tamayo Pacheco, Francisco: 1957 (Box 20)
  - Taylor, Paul Schuster: 1944-1947 (Box 20)
  - Taylor, Paul Schuster: 1948-1955 (Box 20)
  - Taylor, Paul Schuster: 1957-1960 (Box 20)
  - Taylor, Paul Schuster: 1961-1967 (Box 20)
  - Taylor, Thomas H.: 1961 (Box 20)
  - Terrell Family (Edgar Allen Terrell, Sr., and Edgar Allen Terrell, Jr.): 1947-1967 (Box 20)
  - Thomas, Norman Mattoon: 1962-1963 (Box 20)
  - Thornburg, David R.: 1964-1965 (Box 20)
  - Thornton Family (Family of Robert B. and Jayne B. Thornton): 1948-1968 (Box 20)
  - Thorp, Josephine Rice: undated (Box 20)
  - Thurmond, Strom: 1967 (Box 20)
  - Time Magazine:1960 (Box 20)
  - Towle Family (Warren Wilder and Gene Towle): 1968 (Box 20)
  - Townes, Charles Hard: 1958-1966 (Box 20)
  - Townsend, Carrie F. (Hudgens) (Sister of Robert W. Hudgens): 1950-1968 (Box 20)
  - Tugwell, Rexford Guy: 1962 (Box 20)
  - Tunnell, Spencer: 1949-1963 (Box 20)
  - United Church of Christ of Chapel Hill: 1960-1966 (Box 21)
  - United Church of Christ of Chapel Hill: 1967-1968 (Box 21)
  - United Church of Christ of Chapel Hill: 1969 (Box 21)
  - United Church of Christ of Chapel Hill: 1970 (Box 21)
  - United Church of Christ of Chapel Hill: 1971-1972 (Box 21)
  - United Lutheran Church in America: 1961 (Box 21)
  - United Nations: 1962-1972 (Box 21)
  - United Nations Association of the United States of America: 1959-1968 (Box 21)
  - U.S. Farmers Home Administration: 1938-1962 (Box 22)
  - U.S. Farmers Home Administration: 1963-1972 (Box 22)
  - U.S. Farmers Home Administration: Newsletters: 1957-1971 (Box 22)
  - U.S. Farmers Home Administration: Newsletters:1972 (Box 22)
  - University Club: 1948-1963 (Box 22)
  - University of California, Berkeley: 1955-1960 (Box 22)
  - Vaugh, Jack Hood: 1964-1966 (Box 23)
  - Vinson, Fred: 1961 (Box 23)
  - Vogel, Emma E.: 1948 (Box 23)
  - Vogt, William: 1952-1967 (Box 23)
  - Voorhis, Horace Jerry: 1947 (Box 23)
  - Vorse, Mary Heaton: 1954-1960 (Box 23)
  - Vrooman, Carl Schurz: 1958 (Box 23)
  - Walker, John A.: 1947-1948 (Box 23)
  - Wallace, Henry Agard: 1952-1968 (Box 23)
  - Watts Family (Family of J. Washington Watts, a relative of Robert W. Hudgens): 1949-1972 (Box 23)
  - Webb, James Edwin: Sunday (Box 23)
  - Webb, Robert William: 1961-1962 (Box 23)
  - Westbrook Family (Family of Constance Furman Westbrook, sister of Eleanor Furman Hudgens, and her husband, Joseph J. Westbrook): 1947-1970 (Box 23)
  - Wharburton, Clyde Williams: 1948 (Box 23)
  - Wharton, Clifton Reginald: 1963-1972 (Box 23)
  - Will Family (Ralph Reeves and Gladys Will): 1956-1969 (Box 23)
  - Williams, James Thomas: 1935-1969 (Box 23)
  - Willis, Henry Stuart Kendall: 1972 (Box 23)
  - Wilson, Horace: 1949-1963 (Box 23)
  - Wilson Family (John E. and Phyllis Stryker Wilson): 1964-1972 (Box 23)
  - Wiltbank, Milford J.: 1963-1964 (Box 23)
  - Woofter, Thomas Jackson: 1952-1956 (Box 23)
  - Workman, William Douglas: 1964-1969 (Box 23)
  - World Health Organization: 1965 (Box 23)
  - World Neighbors: 1964- 1972 (Box 23)
  - Yoe, Harry Warner: 1954 (Box 23)
  - Realia, undated (Box 24)
  - Poor Rooster's Scrapbook 1954 (Box 25)